this video will explain to you the
该视频将向您说明
intuition behind a new game theoretic
新游戏理论背后的直觉
solution concept called correlated
解决方案概念称为相关
equilibrium let's think again about the
平衡让我们再考虑一下
battle of the sexes game and let's think
两性游戏之战，让我们想一想
about its Nash equilibria remember
关于它的纳什均衡记得
there's a Nash equilibrium where both
纳什均衡
players play B there's a Nash
玩家玩B有纳什
equilibrium where both players play F
双方都发挥F的平衡
and there's another Nash equilibrium
还有另一个纳什均衡
where both players randomize according
两位玩家根据
to these probabilities and that means
这些概率，这意味着
that all four of the outcomes can happen
所有四个结果都可能发生
so both of these outcomes can happen but
所以这两种结果都可能发生，但是
these ones can happen as well now let's
这些事情也可以发生现在，让我们
think about intuitively what makes the
直觉地思考什么使
most sense to us about the battle of the
对我们而言，最了解
sexes it's really that this outcome
性别确实是这个结果
would happen half the time and this
会发生一半的时间，这
outcome would happen half the time all
结果会一半都发生
right if you and your partner really did
如果你和你的伴侣真的做到了
have different preferences about what to
对要做什么有不同的偏好
do and you wanted to be together you
你想和你在一起
would work it out where you each win
会算出您每次获胜的地方
half the time and something that might
一半的时间，可能
have struck you about battle of the
打击了你的战斗
sexes is it doesn't give us a way to say
性别是没有给我们一种表达方式
that that's a stable outcome and the
那是一个稳定的结果，
reason why we don't say it's stable is
我们不说它稳定的原因是
that if both of these things can happen
如果这两种事情都能发生
then both players have to be playing
然后两个玩家都必须玩
mixed strategies with full support and
全面支持下的混合策略
that means the MIS coordination actions
这意味着MIS的协调行动
have to be possible as well well here's
一定也要在这里
another example that we can think about
我们可以考虑的另一个例子
there will give us some intuition for
会给我们一些直觉
why the what's really going on here and
为什么这里真正发生了什么
how we can do something about it so this
我们如何才能做到这一点，所以这
is the traffic game so this models the
是交通游戏，所以这为
situation where two cars are coming
两辆车要来的情况
together to an intersection and they
一起到一个路口，他们
have to decide whether to wait for the
必须决定是否等待
other person to go through first or
别人先经过或
whether to just go through well if if
是否要顺利通过
one of them goes and the other one waits
其中一个去，另一个等待
then the one that goes gets the most
然后去的人得到最大
utility and the one that waits gets a
实用程序和等待的人得到一个
bit less utility if they both wait
如果他们都等的话，实用性会降低
they're both strictly less happy because
他们俩绝对不那么快乐，因为
they both waited and they still have to
他们俩都在等待，他们仍然必须
decide what to do if they both go the
决定如果他们俩都去了该怎么办
worst of all things happens because they
最糟糕的事情发生是因为它们
crash into each other so in total we
撞到对方所以总的来说
have two pure strategy equilibria that
有两个纯策略均衡
again asymmetric kind of like in battle
再次在战斗中不对称
of the sexes and of course it's also
的性别，当然也
possible to have a mixed strategy
可能有混合策略
equilibrium here but let's think about
这里平衡，但让我们考虑一下
what would really happen in the world
世界上到底会发生什么
when we have this kind of situation
当我们有这种情况
where we have an intersection and
我们有一个路口，
there's the possibility that cars might
汽车可能会
collide what we really do is we have a
碰撞我们真正要做的是
traffic light and let's think about what
交通灯，让我们考虑一下
a traffic light means game theoretically
理论上，交通信号灯意味着游戏
it's a fair randomizing device that
这是一个公平的随机装置
recommends actions to the agents it
向代理商推荐行动
tells one of them to go it tells the
告诉其中一个去吧
other one to wait and it's fair in the
另一个要等待，这是公平的
sense that at different times it makes
感觉在不同的时间
different recommendations well the
不同的建议以及
benefits here are that the negative
好处是负面的
payoff outcomes are completely avoided
完全避免了回报结果
we can achieve something fair and in
我们可以做到公平，公正
general although not in this example
一般，虽然在此示例中不
it's possible to end up with a sum of
最终可能总和
social welfare that exceeds that that
超过那个的社会福利
can be achieved in any Nash equilibrium
可以在任何纳什均衡中实现
well we can use the same idea to achieve
好吧，我们可以使用相同的想法来实现
the fair outcome in the battle of the
战役中的公平结果
sexes game so we could have a situation
性别游戏，所以我们可能会遇到这种情况
where the husband and wife flip a coin
夫妻掷硬币的地方
and depending on how the coin comes up
并取决于硬币如何出现
they go together either to the bat
他们一起去蝙蝠
aligner to the football well this is
很适合足球，这是
essentially the idea of a correlated
本质上是相关的
equilibrium the correlated equilibrium
均衡相关均衡
is a randomized assignment of action
是随机分配的动作
recommendations to the agents such that
给代理商的建议
everybody wants to follow the action
每个人都想跟随行动
recommendations so we have some
建议，所以我们有一些
randomizing device that tells me be some
告诉我随机装置
of the time and F some of the time
的时间和F的一些时间
and it's it and in a correlated way
就是这样，并且以一种相关的方式
potentially correlated way tells you be
潜在相关的方式告诉你
some of the time and tells you have some
有些时候告诉你有一些
of the time so flipping a coin where if
在时间上如此抛硬币如果
it's heads we both get the
我们都得到了
recommendation be if it's tails we both
推荐是如果我们都是尾巴
get the recommendation F is a
得到推荐F是一个
randomizing device like this although
虽然这样的随机装置
it's possible for it to be more
可能会更多
complicated and I in principle if it
复杂，我原则上是否
comes up heads and we understand that to
冒出头，我们了解到
mean that we're both getting the
意味着我们都得到了
recommendation B this doesn't compel us
建议B这不会强迫我们
both to go to the ballet we still get to
都去芭蕾舞，我们仍然要去
freely decide how to interpret that
自由决定如何解释
recommendation but it's a correlated
推荐，但这是相关的
equilibrium if neither of us would want
如果我们两个都不愿意的话
to deviate from the recommendation and
偏离建议
you can see in this example with battle
你可以在这个例子中看到战斗
of the sexes that indeed neither of us
的性别，实际上我们俩都不
would want to deviate because if the
会想偏离，因为如果
other one is following
另一个正在关注
recommendation and I deviate then I'm
建议，我偏离了我
just gonna get a payoff of zero instead
只会得到零的回报
of getting a positive payoff so a
获得正收益的过程
correlated equilibrium is any such
相关均衡就是这样
randomized assignment of these possibly
这些可能的随机分配
correlated action recommendations that
相关的行动建议
leaves nobody wanting to deviate it's a
留下没人想偏离它的
generalization of the idea of Nash
纳什思想的概括
equilibrium because if these action
平衡，因为如果这些动作
recommendations are not correlated at
的建议在以下位置不相关
all then we just get back to mixed
然后我们回到混合状态
strategies like we had before so we can
像以前一样的策略，所以我们可以
capture any Nash equilibrium this way
以此方式捕获任何纳什均衡
but we can also get new things like
但我们也可以得到诸如
we've just seen so it's this strict kind
我们刚刚看到过，所以这是一种严格的要求
of weakening of the concept of Nash
纳什概念的削弱
equilibrium and includes more things and
平衡，包括更多的事物和
it can get us these kinds of nice fair
它可以给我们带来这样的公平
outcomes
结果